Mobile: 0162 9012 603

Email: hungaoisysvn@gmail.com

Nguyen Nam Hung

Objective

Seeking a leading role contributing to improved business growth, technical growth and technical development. The position which allows me to inject energy and be enthusiastic to motivate and inspire staff, and deliver outstanding results.

Profile

I have 5 years working in the IT industry at companies in Vietnam with position such as programming. I repeatedly asked to complete self-leaning to become good software engineer. I always try and know how to overcome challenges to complete all tasks in job position. Enthusiasm is the key to my success.

Computer skills

- Developing and maintaining the infrastructure and IT systems.
- Languages: Java, JavaScript, SQL, CSS, HTML, JSP
- Software: Eclipse IDEA, IntelliJ IDEA, Netbeans IDEA, Apache Tomcat, Maven, MySQL, Oracle, SQL Server, Redmine, Jira, Postman, TortoiseSVN, TortoiseGit.

Languages

Reading English technical documents and other materials fluently.

Education

Bach Khoa University of HCM City

Bachelor of Science - Computer Science

Graduation thesis

Software development for children learning English on Android devices. Application provides learn English through: Flashcard, Game, Video, Song, Tories.

Personal Detail

• Marital status: Single

• **Birthday**: Jan 20 1992

• Interests: Reading, sport and music

Nationality: Viet Nam

Professional experience

November 2019 – Now. Software Engineering

GMS Logistic.

- Start with the WMS project. Responsible for developing shipment module.
- Role:
 - Full Stack developer:
 - Front-end: Create new UI with Nexacro Framework. and use Javascript control, Vuejs.
 - Back-end: Java Spring with REST Web service.
 - Responsible for the development of new features, build REST APIs Web Service.
- Achievements: learn new technical, business knowledge warehouse management.
- Team size: ~4 members

October 2018 – October 2019 Software Engineering

SCB Bank.

- Role:
 - Full Stack developer:
 - Front-end: Create new UI with VueJs Framework. and use Javascript control.
 - Back-end: Java 8 Spring with REST Web service, NodeJs.
 - Responsible for the development of new features, build and maintain REST APIs Web Service.
- Achievements: learn new technical
- Team size: ~5 members

August 2017 – July 2018 Software Engineering

Rakumo.

- Start with the Open House project, real estate management system, work with Japanese via redmine software.
- Programing languages: Java, JavaScript, SQL, CSS
- Skills used: Java Core, Spring, Javascript, Css, Json, Jax-Ws, ORM MyBatis, MySQL, Git, Grunt, Webpack, Intellij IDE; business knowledge.
- Role:
 - Full Stack developer:
 - Front-end: Create new UI with Dhtmlx Framwork and use Javascript control.
 - Back-end: Java 8 Spring with REST Web service.
 - Responsible for the development of new features, build and maintain REST APIs Web Service.
- Achievements: learn new technical
- Team size: ~4 members

Professional experience

July 2015 – July 2017. Software Engineering

- **CSC Software.**
- Start with the SOMPO's project, health insurance system.
- Role:
 - Full Stack developer:
 - Front-end: Create new UI with JSP, jquey and use Javascript, Ajax to control.
 - Back-end: Java Hibernate.
 - Responsible for the development of new features, build and maintain health insurance system.
- Achievements: learn new technical, business knowledge insurance
- Team size: ~30 members